晚上好  路易吉披萨[意大利语]
Buona sera, Luigi's Pizza.
晚上好[意大利语]
Buona sera.
这是意大利语的"晚上好"
It means good evening in Italian.
我想说  跟你解释这个问题
May I say, having to explain that to you calls into question
让我对你们"餐厅"的正宗性产生了怀疑
the authenticity of your ristorante?
我出去了
Okay, I'm out of here.
稍等[意大利语]
Un momento.
我的老天爷呀
Oh, for heaven's sake.
现在你是真心在装傻了吧
Now you're being deliberately stupid.
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
我要去拉杰那儿跟普丽娅共进晚餐
I'm having dinner with Priya at Raj's.
我觉得霍华德也会去  你也来吗
I think Howard's going to be there. You want to join us?
可今天是星期四啊
But tonight's Thursday.
每个星期四大家都会过来
On Thursdays, everybody comes over here
一起吃披萨
and has pizza.
或者是看菜单挺正宗
Or a reasonable facsimile
说是由某位叫路易吉做的
prepared by someone claiming to be Luigi,
可电话里的声音却听着山寨得像成龙
but who sounds suspiciously like Jackie Chan.
咱们今晚就不能破例一次吗
Can't we make a one-time exception for tonight?
行啊
We could.
咱今晚也可以不用字母"M"
We could also stop using the letter "M,"
但我觉得这主意挺"呼导"[误导]挺"奥残"[脑残]的
but I think that idea is isguided and oronic.
跟我一起去拉杰家吧
Just come with me to Raj's.
我不想参加派对
Well, I don't want to go to a party.
不是派对  就是原来的一群
It's not a party. It's the same group of people
在这里聚的人今天去那里聚
who hang out here hanging out over there.
不好意思  但是五个人一起吃饭聊天就是派对
I'm sorry, but five people eating and chatting is a party.
那为啥在咱们这儿不算派对
How come it's not a party when we do it here?
因为我们从来不办派对啊
Because we don't throw parties.
我不知道该怎么跟你说了  谢尔顿
I don't know what to tell you, Sheldon.
我要去见普丽娅  大家都去的
I'm going to see Priya. Everyone's over there.
你来不来
You coming or not?
当然不去  知道为啥吗
Well, no, sir, and do you know why?
一个词
In a word:
传统
tradition.
在过去这八年的每个周四晚上
Every Thursday night for the last eight years,
你和我还有我们的朋友们聚在这里
you and I and our friends have gathered here
就在这里切开覆盖着起司和酱料的面包[暗指披萨]
in this very spot to break bread covered with cheese and sauce,
讨论当日话题
discuss the issues of the day,
没错  还有分享欢乐
and yes, share a laugh or two.
但我猜这些宝贵的回忆对你来说一文不值
But I guess our rich heritage means nothing to you.
你说的没错
I guess you're right.
-回见  -等等
- See you later. - Wait!
莱纳德  等等
Leonard! Wait!
那我晚上吃啥啊
What am I going to do for dinner?
跟我一起去拉杰家吃饭啊
Come with me to Raj's and eat there.
我可不干
I can't do that.
万一他做了羊杂碎和黑香肠呢
What if he serves haggis and blood pudding?
我对他会上这两道菜深表怀疑
I really doubt that's what he'll serve.
万一他做了呢
But what if he does?
我就不得不
I'll be obliged to dine
吃包在羊肚里煮熟的肝和肺了
on liver and lungs stuffed in a sheep's stomach.
说实在的  黑香肠差不多也是一样的
And frankly, blood pudding is essentially the same thing.
我不知道他为啥整这俩菜
I don't know why he's serving both.
你到底想干啥
What do you want to do?
是跟我一起去还是一个人待在家里
You want to come with me, or do you want to sit here alone?
算了  我还是去你的杂碎派对吧
No, I'll go to your haggis party.
但我得跟你说
But I'm telling you.
这太"轰狂"[疯狂]了  绝对是太"轰狂"[疯狂]了
This is adness. This is utter and complete adness.
生活大爆炸
第四季第十七集
天啊
Oh, dear!
-咋了  -拉杰的电视
- What? - Raj's television.
我刚才意识到
I just realized
我们整晚都得看着
we're about to spend an evening watching a plasma screen
左上角还有一坨坏点的等离子电视
with a cluster of dead pixels in the upper left-hand corner.
那就别看电视了呗
So don't watch TV.
看书吧
Read a book.
想显得不合群吗
And be a social pariah?
你知道那不是哥的风格
Oh, you know that's not my style.
你叹气是因为懊恼  对吧
The audible sigh is a show of exasperation, right?
对
Right.
是因为我还是坏点
Is it about me or the dead pixels?
嗨  你俩来得正好
Hey, you're just in time.
我们做了德墨风味的小菜
We made Tex-Mex.
听起来不错哦
Oh, sounds great.
印度佬做德墨菜啊
Oh, Indians making Tex-Mex.
还不如吃中式披萨呢
Might as well have had the Chinese pizza.
你来啦
Hey, you.
嗨
Hi.
对你来说肯定很有意思  对吧
That's got to be fun for you, huh?
看着霍夫斯塔德在你妹妹嘴里
Watching Hofstadter suck the saliva
吮吸唾液
out of your sister's mouth?
不好意思  在今晚开始之前
Excuse me. Before this evening goes any further,
我们得先定好谁坐在哪儿
we need to decide where everyone is going to sit.
又没有人预定座位  谢尔顿
There is no assigned seats, Sheldon.
随便找个地儿坐呗  别太拘束哈
Just sit anywhere. Make yourself comfortable.
真有意思
Oh, what fun.
我们就像是友爱集会里的嬉皮士
We're like hippies at a love-in.
就坐这儿吧
Just sit here.
马上  哥们儿  马上
Right on, man. Right on.
看呐
Oh, look.
这不是哈利波特和百分之九十八的魔法石吗
it's Harry Potter and 98% of The Sorcerer's Stone.
好咯  这里有玉米卷饼
Okay, we've got fajitas
和各种配菜  你们自便吧
with all the fixins, so you make your own.
好极了
Wonderful.
晚饭  还得要自己动手的
Dinner, some assembly required.
想来一杯玛格丽特吗  谢尔顿
Do you want a margarita, Sheldon?
玛格丽特
A margarita?!
我们这是在哪儿啊  出什么事儿了
Where are we?! What is happening?!
嗨  谢尔顿
Oh. Hey, Sheldon.
想来点儿啥
What can I get you?
水  纯水
Water. Neat.
再放一把小伞
With a little umbrella.
你的朋友们在哪儿呢
Where are all your friends?
可悲啊  佩妮  今晚  我就是黑暗骑士[蝙蝠侠]
Sadly, Penny, this evening, I am the Dark Knight,
独自漫步在破旧的大街上
roaming these mean streets alone.
一件斗篷风衣披肩
A windbreaker for my cape,
帽檐下是冷峻的面庞
and a stern expression for my cowl.
好吧
Okay.
劳驾
Excuse me?
难道现在不是应该有一位厌世的酒保
Isn't this the point where the world-weary barkeep
心不在焉地一边擦柜台
absentmindedly wipes down the bar
一遍抚慰客人心中的忧愁吗
and coaxes the woes out of the troubled patron?
我只是要帮你拿那个该死的小伞  不过好吧
Well, I was getting your stupid umbrella, but all right.
有什么烦心事啊  伙计
What's troubling you, buddy?
我知道你是装出来的  不过既然你问了
I don't think your heart's in it, but since you asked...
显然  因为莱纳德在和拉杰的妹妹约会
Apparently, because Leonard is dating Raj's sister,
我们都被迫去拉杰家里聚会
we're all forced to hang out at his apartment.
哦  真糟糕
Oh, the horror.
没错
Indeed.
而且啊  拉杰在放雷鬼音乐[源自牙买加]
Yeah, at one point, Raj put on reggae music,
他妹妹还把鞋给脱了
and his sister took off her shoes.
简直就是卡里古拉大帝的晚年时期
It was like the last days of Caligula.
这个我得接
Oh, I have to get this.
伞呢
Umbrella?
真不知道她有啥好恼的
Wonder what she's exasperated about.
嗨
Hello?
谢尔顿  你还好吧
Sheldon, are you all right?
我们上次通话的时候  你正准备
When last we spoke, you were going to
打车离开拉杰家  但是根据Facebook
take a taxi home from Raj's, but according to Facebook,
你刚才进蛋糕工厂了
you just checked in at the Cheesecake Factory.
对  我之前是在打车来着
Yes, I was in a taxi,
但是司机和他运营执照上的照片
but the driver didn't look at all
长得一点都不像
like the photograph on his license,
所以我就跳下车跑过来了
so I leapt out and ran for it.
明智
Wise.
给你
There you go.
就像是加勒比海边的元气恢复酒一样
Just like recovering alcoholics drink in the Caribbean.
嗨  闺蜜
Hi, bestie.
哦嗨  艾米
Oh. Hi, Amy.
最近还好吗
How you been?
很好
Fine.
从这个角度  我能看到你的鼻孔
From this angle, I can see up your nose.
是啊  活在高科技时代挺好的  对吧
Yeah, it's a great time to be alive, isn't it?
没关系  我的问题可以待会儿再说
Don't worry. My problems can wait
你们两个女人接着八卦吧
while you two hens finish your clucking.
听着  谢尔顿  莱纳德在和普丽娅约会
Look, Sheldon, Leonard is dating Priya.
她住在拉杰那儿
She is staying with Raj.
这就意味着你们以后很可能会经常去那儿
That means you're all probably gonna be hanging out there more.
佩妮  很抱歉把你也牵扯进来
Penny, I'm sorry you got dragged into this.
我知道你伤心欲绝
I know you're devastated
你的前男友找到了一位惊艳的新欢
that your ex-boyfriend has found an exciting new lover
而且她的小麦色皮肤美丽无瑕
with flawless, caramel-colored skin.
我对莱纳德和普丽娅的事儿没啥郁闷的
Okay, I'm not upset about Leonard and Priya.
但你扇动的鼻翼可不是这个意思
Your flaring nostrils indicate otherwise.
继续八吧八吧
Cluck-cluck-cluck.
谢尔顿  看着我
Sheldon, look at me.
我觉得是时候
I think it's time
面对这一现实了
to face the fact
莱纳德就是你们这个小团体的中心
that Leonard is the nucleus of your social group.
他去哪儿  你们就去哪儿
Where he goes, the group goes.
莱纳德是中心
Leonard the nucleus?
这没道理啊
That makes no sense.
我才是异想天开的精灵
I'm the whimsical elf
让大家欢乐相聚
that everyone looks to for a good time.
我不是说你很无聊
I'm not saying that you're not fun.
你是我认识的最有趣的人
You're the most fun person I know.
很多人觉得跟我一起很有趣
A lot of people think I'm fun to be around.
别耍宝了  闺蜜
Don't be needy, bestie.
也许正是因此莱纳德离开了你
That's probably part of what chased Leonard away.
我的意思是  谢尔顿
What I am saying, Sheldon,
你们那群人是以莱纳德为中心的
is that your group is Leonard-centric.
要是个小镇  就会是莱纳德镇
If it were a town, it would be Leonardville.
要是个伊斯兰国家  莱纳德斯坦
If it were an Islamic nation, Leonardstan.
要是电影的诞生地
If it were the birthplace of motion pictures,
大家都会唱着"莱纳坞精神万岁"
we'd all be singing "Hooray for Leonardwood."
我想到一个
Ooh, I got one.
如果你们是支乐队
If you guys were a band,
就会是莱纳德和他朋友们
you'd be called Leonard and the Leonards.
太耍宝了
So needy.
你在做什么
What you doing?
拿点小吃出来
I'm setting out snacks.
今晚我们都要去拉杰家你知道的吧
You do realize everyone's eating at Raj's again tonight.
这小吃又不是给你的  诺丝·罗茜
I didn't say the snacks were for you now, did I, Nosy Rosie?
有人要来吗
You're having people over?
对  你一定好奇死了谁会来
Yes. Must be killing you wondering who.
好吧  我告诉你
Fine, I'll tell you.
是漫画书店的斯图尔特
Stuart from the comic bookstore,
同事巴里·克瑞普克
Barry Kripke from the university,
佩妮的前男友扎克
Penny's ex-boyfriend Zack
演员勒瓦尔·布尔顿
and TV's LeVar Burton.
真的吗
Really?
勒瓦尔·布尔顿也要来吗
LeVar Burton's coming here?
可能  我在推特上联系他了
Possibly. I Tweeted him.
好吧  告诉他我喜欢他在《星际迷航》的表演
Okay, well, tell him I loved him on Star Trek.
拜托  莱纳德  别想打扰我新朋友
Please, Leonard, stop trying to horn in on my new friends.
当然  晚安
Of course. Good night.
-莱纳德  -什么
- Leonard. - Yeah?
之前你我共度了许多美好时光
We had a good run, you and I.
好--吧
Okay.
但变化本就是人生的一部分
But change is a part of life.
当然是
It certainly is.
好了
Okay.
我有客人要来
I have guests coming.
恐怕得请你赶紧走了
I'm afraid I'm going to have to ask you to leave now.
我正要走了
I am leaving.
别让离别变得更加不舍  莱纳德
Don't make this harder than it is, Leonard.
再见  谢尔顿
Good-bye, Sheldon.
你也再见  先生
And good-bye to you, sir.
他会回来的
He'll be back.
我当然会回来  我住这儿
Of course I'll be back. I live here!
好吧  看来
Well, it would appear
勒瓦尔·布尔顿是不会来了
LeVar Burton won't be joining us.
我们开始吧
Let's get started.
开始先在屋里四处走走
I thought we'd begin by going around the room,
介绍下自己
introducing ourselves
稍微说下自己为何来这
and saying a little bit about why we're here.
好了  我是谢尔顿
Okay. I'm Sheldon.
对于经常阅读
Uh, for regular readers
《新英格兰高能物理学》杂志的人来说
of The New England Journal of High Energy Physics,
我不需要介绍自己了
I need no introduction.
如果你不熟悉那本刊物
If you're not familiar with that publication,
礼品袋里有免费样书赠送
there's a free copy in your goody bag.
斯图尔特
Stuart?
大家好  我是斯图尔特
Um... Hi. I'm Stuart.
我开了家漫画书店
I run a comic bookstore,
因经济原因  我最近还住在店里
which for financial reasons, I'm currently living in.
我今晚到这最希望的是能洗个热水澡
I guess what I'm hoping for most out of tonight is a hot shower.
很好  斯图尔特
It's very nice, Stuart.
扎克
Zack?
我是扎克  我呃...
I'm Zack, and I'm, uh...
这...
uh...
我等下再说行吗
Could you come back to me?
当然
Of course.
巴里
Barry?
我是巴里·克瑞普克  我来这里
I'm Barry Kwipke, and I'm here
是因为你说今晚会有"凑奖"
because you told me there was going to be a whaffle.
凑奖什么时候开始
When is the whaffle?
淡定  淡定  巴里
Patience, patience, Barry.
凑奖...
The whaffle...
抽奖是持续整晚
The raffle is the grand finale
玩乐放荡的压轴大戏
to an evening-long festival of fun and folly.
-还有个问题  -对  你一定会抽得到
- One more question... - Yes, you must be present to win.
好了  我准备好了
Okay, I'm ready.
我是扎克  我呃...
I'm Zach, and I'm, uh...
讨厌  为什么这么难
Oh, crap, why is this so hard?
嗨
Oh, hey.
-嗨  -好啊  宅女
- Hi. - Yo, P-dog.
有事吗
What's up?
我们来绑架你出去过女生之夜
We're here to kidnap you for a girls' night out.
说明一下  所谓"绑架"是开玩笑的
Parenthetical: the term "Kidnap" is being used playfully.
我知道的
I kind of figured that.
很好  那就把这枕头套套上去
Good. Now put this pillowcase over your head.
不要
No.
她以前比这有趣多了
She used to be much more fun,
直到莱纳德狠狠伤了她的心
until Leonard punched her in the heart.
我们认为你应该想出去
We just thought you might want to go out
好好玩一下  或者去跳跳舞
and have a good time, maybe go dancing.
天  谢谢  可我现在没心情
Oh. Gee, thanks, but I'm not really in the mood.
你要知道  沉醉到其他各种
You do understand that it will distract you
甜蜜可爱事情上  能让你不去注意
from obsessing over the rich variety of sweet loving
你的前男友
that your ex-boyfriend
正得到孟买火热宝贝的青睐
is currently receiving from the fiery jewel of Mumbai.
好吧
Okay, look,
我要是同意跟你们出去玩
if I agree to go out with you guys,
你们要保证不拿莱纳德和普丽娅的事烦我
will you promise to stop pestering me about Leonard and Priya?
-好的  -当然
- Yes. - Sure.
好吧  我去换衣服  进来吧
All right. I'll go change. Come on in.
你要是让我带了哥罗芳[迷药]
If you'd have let me bring the chloroform,
我们就不必说刚才那么多废话了
we wouldn't have had to put up with all this jibber-jabber.
总之  我们滑雪滑累了之后
Anyway, after we get done snowboarding,
我就回旅馆  泡极可意按摩浴缸了
I go back to the lodge and get in the Jacuzzi.
周围没有人  所以我自然就让蛋蛋出来呼吸了
There's no one around, so naturally, I'm free-balling it.
然后
Next thing I know,
有位美女突然出现
this beautiful chick shows up,
喝得醉醺醺地  想跟我共浴
drunk out of her skull, wants to get in with me.
提问
Question.
那是极可意浴缸还是热水浴缸
Was it a Jacuzzi or a hot tub?
你坑爹呢?  就想问这个?!
Really? That's your question?
有什么区别
What's the difference?
极可意浴缸是种商业品牌
"Jacuzzi" is a commercial brand.
热水浴缸是通用术语
"Hot tub" is the generic term.
就是说  所有极可意都是热水浴缸
I.E., all Jacuzzis are hot tubs,
但并非所有热水浴缸都是极可意
but not all hot tubs are Jacuzzis.
是不是就像所有拇指都是手指
Is that like all thumbs are fingers,
但并非所有手指都是拇指
but not all fingers are thumbs?
没想到啊  是的
Surprisingly, yes.
很好
Nice.
那脚趾到底是什么
Now, what exactly are toes?
能否跳回去继续说那醉妞
Can you please get back to the drunk girl?
我洗澡的时候需要点想象的灵感啊
I'd like something to think about in the shower.
对了
Oh, yeah.
总之  她也脱光光了
Right. Anyway, she takes off all of her clothes,
爬进了热水浴缸  我首先注意到的是...
climbs into the hot tub, and the first thing I notice...
水面上升了
The water level rose.
不是
No.
水位当然要上升
Of course it did.
据说阿基米德
It's said that Archimedes,
古希腊数学家
the ancient Greek mathematician,
就是泡澡时发现了浮力定律
discovered the principle of displacement while taking a bath.
太棒了  继续说  扎克
Terrific. Go ahead, Zack.
光光的醉妞  光光的蛋蛋  继续
Naked drunk girl, free-balling, continue.
抱歉  但我觉得你们会发现
Forgive me, but I think you'll find
我的故事更有趣
my story is more interesting.
你的故事里也有沾露娇乳吗
Does yours have wet breasts in it?
比这更好
Better.
里面有个金冠
It has a gold crown.
国王想知道金冠中有多少黄金
You see, the king wondered how much gold was in it
让阿基米德想个办法测出来
and charged Archimedes with coming up with the solution.
因为金冠形状不规则
Because the crown was irregularly shaped,
无法用数学计算出体积
there was no way to mathematically determine its volume.
但在泡澡时  阿基米德突然想到
But, while bathing, Archimedes realized
可以把金冠浸入水中
he could immerse the crown
量出水面上升的数值以计算体积
and measure the amount the water rose.
长话短说  我上了她
So, long story short, I nailed her.
想出来后  他高叫着"我找到了"[希腊语]
When he finished, he shouted "Eureka!"
不  我总是叫"天哪"
No, I always shout, "Holy moly!"
不知道为什么  反正就这么叫
Don't know why. Just do.
好吧
All right,
今晚的"让我们了解你"部分到此为止
that concludes the "Getting to know you" Portion of the evening.
谁想来玩些复古游戏
Who's ready to play some vintage video games?
今晚的选择包括
And tonight's selections include
ColecoVision的"蓝精灵救援之格格巫城堡"
ColecoVision's "Smurf Rescue in Gargamel's Castle,"
雅达利的"饼干怪兽大口嚼"[是一款《芝麻街》电玩]
Atari's "Cookie Monster Munch,"
以及给你们这种文字冒险游戏迷准备的
and for you text adventure aficionados,
"索克"
"Zork."
选我选我  我可好玩啦
Pick me, pick me. I'm fun.
里面那个长毛大肉球可恶心了
That all sucks the big hairy meatball.
我去把我车上的卡拉OK机拿出来
How about I go get the karaoke machine out of my car,
喝个酩酊大醉  然后把放声高歌把屋顶掀飞  怎么样
get plastered and blow the roof off this place?
很好  我负责买啤酒
Great, I'll make a beer run.
那我负责去洗澡
And I'll take a shower.
15分钟后见
We'll meet back here in 15.
就这么定了
Check.
我负责不高兴
I'm unhappy.
真好吃
This is delicious.
你这辣椒汤在哪儿学的
Where'd you learn to make chili?
我在英国读大学的时候
When I was at university in England,
我室友是得克萨斯州人
my flatmate was from Texas.
希望她不跟我那位得克萨斯室友一样
I hope she wasn't anything like my flatmate from Texas.
谢尔顿有点古怪  对吧
Sheldon is a bit quirky, isn't he?
拜托  回顾那个混蛋疯子的人生
Oh, please. That crazy bastard's looking
全都是古怪这个词儿呢
at quirky in the rearview mirror.
你们知道吗  我们的室友协议里面规定
Did you know that, per our roommate agreement,
我必须在洗澡前先把脚洗干净
I have to wash my feet before I get in the shower?
而且还不能在水池子里洗
And not in the sink.
所以我们各有一个特制的小桶
We each have special buckets.
拉杰  你有告诉过你妹妹
Raj, did you ever tell your sister
谢尔顿曾被比尔·盖茨扁过吗
about the time Sheldon got punched by Bill Gates?
-天啊  你开玩笑呢吧  -真的
- Oh, God, you're kidding. - Nope.
盖茨来大学里演讲
Gates gave a speech at the university.
结束后  谢尔顿走过去跟他说
Sheldon went up to him afterwards and said,
"如果你不是为非洲的病童
"Maybe if you weren't so distracted
那么劳神的话
by sick children in Africa,
或许你能有多一点想法  好好弄弄Windows Vista"
you could have put a little more thought into Windows Vista."
砰  正中鼻头
Bam. Right in the nose.
顿时让我觉得  拥有一台电脑是多么骄傲的事情
Made me proud to own a PC.
我提议为今晚举杯欢庆
I'd like to propose a toast
为这完全摆脱谢尔顿的珍贵而美妙的夜晚
to a rare and wonderful Sheldon-free evening.
-说得对  -干杯
- Hear, hear. - Cheers.
你们发现这是破天荒头一遭  我们举杯欢庆
You realize that's the first time we've ever done that
而不被谢尔顿强迫科普
without having to listen to Sheldon tell us
何为祝酒吗
why it's called a toast?
那何为祝酒
Why is it called a toast?
古罗马人
Oh, the ancient Romans
把香喷喷的面包片放到他们的酒碗里
put spiced toast in their punch bowls.
谢尔顿解释得更好
Sheldon tells it better.
-好像是  -的确是
- He kind of does. - Yeah.
该死的  我想他了
Aw, hell, I miss him.
那你们想去哪里跳舞
So, where do you guys want to go dancing?
我们希望你会知道个好地方
We were hoping you'd know a place.
对  或许那里上演着
Yes, perhaps somewhere packed tightly
一场超棒的肉体狂欢会
with young, beautiful bodies
紧身的衣服藏不住年轻美丽的躯体
sweating and writhing against each other
大家挥洒着汗水  相互扭成一团
in a glorious orgy of the flesh.
没错  我是知道这么个地方
Oh, yeah, I know that place.
这身怎么样
What do you think?
应该能充分展示你的胸襟
That should display enough of your bosom
好吸引一个新男友  或是一个饥饿的婴儿
to attract a new mate, or a hungry infant.
够了  我再跟你们重申一次
Okay, let's go through this one more time.
只因莱纳德有了新女友
Just because Leonard has a new girlfriend
并不意味着我要出去勾引一个新男友
does not mean I need to go out and hook up with some guy.
但如果你想你就可以  不是吗
But you could if you wanted to, right?
话是这么说  没错
Well, yeah, I guess.
从房间里挑选出一位最辣的猛男
Pick out the hottest guy in the room,
把他带回家  跟他做一些不能说的秘密
take him home, do unspeakable things to him,
然后让他面带微笑  臀带牙印
then kick him to the curb with a smile on his face
滚到路边
and teeth marks on his heinie?
差不多吧
More or less.
那是种怎样的滋味呀
What's that like?
我也说不清
I don't know.
当你做的时候  乐在其中
It's fun while you're doing it.
但过后  大多时候会尴尬
And then after, it's mostly embarrassment,
自我厌恶和后悔
self-loathing and regret.
我愿意整天都享受这种滋味
I would take that deal all day long.
好吧  但今晚不会发生这种事
Yeah, well, it's not gonna happen tonight.
这是我人生中第一次
You know, for the first time in my life,
不谈恋爱
I am not in a relationship,
我也完全觉得没有关系
and I'm totally okay with it.
如果独自一人对你来说很新鲜
You know, if being on your own is new to you,
我很乐意跟你分享一些  我这么多年来爱用的
I'd be happy to share some tension-relieving techniques
解除空窗期紧张的女士专用科技产品
for ladies I've perfected over the years.
比如  你有电动牙刷吗
For example, do you have an electric toothbrush?
没有
Um, no.
那你应该买一个
You should get one.
那是什么
What's that?
好像是保存的某些东西
It appears to be something preserved
夹在两片丙烯酸树脂之间
between two pieces of acrylic.
那是来自北极的雪花片
Oh, it's a snowflake from the North Pole.
莱纳德去年给我的
Leonard gave it to me last year.
天啊  真浪漫
Oh, God, that is so romantic.
是呀  曾经是
Yeah, it was.
莱纳德真是独一无二的情种
Leonard's really one of a kind.
一边拿着雪花一边说这话
Saying that while holding a snowflake
不觉得手上的东西有点儿沉么
is a bit heavy-handed, don't you think?
让我看看
Let me see that.
去它的破雪花
Oh, screw it.
一点半点的自我厌恶  姐还是能处理的
I can deal with a little self-loathing.
走吧  找个小翘臀让姐咬一口
Let's go find me a heinie to bite.
人才呀
Outstanding.
如果失败了  我们可以在CVS停车
And if we fail, we can always stop at CVS
然后给你买个厉害的电动牙刷
and pick you out a nice toothbrush.
我管我的牙刷叫"杰拉德"
I call mine "Gerard."
这有点太怪了
That's kind of creepy.
* 不要让我心碎 *
* Don't go breaking my heart *
* 如果我奋力一搏  结果也枉然 *
* I couldn't if I tried *
* 亲爱的  如果我焦躁不安 *
* Oh, honey, if I get restless *
* 宝贝  你不是这种人 *
* Baby, you're not that kind *
* 不要让我心碎 *
* Don't go breaking my heart *
有人唱《走在阳光里》了吗
Anybody do "Walking on Sunshine" Yet?
没有
No.
那我定啦
Dibs.
抱歉  你是说谢尔顿买了台织布机
I'm sorry, Sheldon bought a loom
然后学习织布吗
and learned how to weave?
他其实学得挺好的
He actually got pretty good.
他给我们都做一件相配的毛毯
He made us all matching serapes.
每当寒风刺骨的时候  我还会拿出来披上
I still wear mine when there's a nip in the air.
那是在他养那25只猫
Now, was this before
的之前还是之后
or after he adopted the 25 cats?
在养猫很久之前
Long before the cats.
我觉得好像是在他试着宣告
I think it was around the time he tried
我们的公寓是个主权国家的那段时间
to declare our apartment a sovereign nation.
我至今还留有些货币呢
I still have some of the currency.
我的朋友们
All my friends.
我觉得就跟《 阴间大法师》一样
I think it's like Beetlejuice.
咱们刚才总是念叨谢尔顿
We said his name too many times.
-快进来  -谢谢
- Come on in. - Thank you.
我还以为你跟你的新朋友在一起呢
Hey. I thought you were with your new buddies.
我必须得离开
I had to leave.
他们的玩乐方式有误
They were having fun wrong.
过来  谢尔顿  跟我坐
Come here, Sheldon. Sit here with me.
谢谢
Thank you.
你来点私房辣椒汤吗
Would you like some homemade chili?
汤里有豆子吗
Are there beans in it?
有
Yes.
那就不是辣椒汤
Then it's not chili.
地道的辣椒汤是没有豆子的
Real chili has no beans in it,
但由于你是来自异乡人
but you're from a foreign land,
你的无知可以被谅解
so your ignorance is forgiven.
谢尔顿  你要还是不要
Sheldon, do you want some or not?
要  谢谢
Yes, please.
你女人的脾气有点毛躁呀
Your girlfriend's a little short-tempered.
我提议举杯欢庆
I'd like to propose a toast
致朋友们  不管他有多古怪
to friends, no matter how quirky.
干杯
Cheers.
普丽娅  你知道何为祝酒吗
Priya, do you know why this is called a toast?
这我还真知道
Actually, I do.
是罗马人把香喷喷的面包
I believe the Romans used to put spiced toast
放进他们的酒碗里
in their punch bowls.
她还有点假装博学多闻
She's also a bit of a know-it-all.
这挺好吃的
Mmm. This is good.
先不管地不地道吧
Whatever it is.
* 我走在阳光里 *
* I'm walking on sunshine *
你好  我
Hello? I...
* 我走在阳光里 *
* I'm walking on sunshine *
我还是走吧
Oh, I don't think so.
推特什么的玩儿蛋去吧
I am so done with Twitter.